Many see friendships as a comfort blanket: a shoulder to cry on, a reliable soul to confide in.
许多人把友谊视为一条安抚毯：一副可以靠着哭一场的肩膀，一个可以倾诉心事的可靠之人。
However, more often than not, in our eagerness to seek individual success, we lose friends along the way and that has become part of the process.
然而，由于急于追求个人成功，我们往往在这一路上失去朋友，而这已成了追求成功过程的一部分。
The chaos and never-ending turmoil that accompanies everyday life is an aggressive obstacle in the pursuit of stable friendships.
在追求稳定友谊的过程中，伴随日常生活而来的混乱和无休无止的动荡是一个极大的障碍。
As students, we use this excuse to shrug off losing people who we once thought to be loved ones.
作为学生，我们以此为借口，对失去那些曾经以为是挚爱的人满不在乎。
Instead of viewing our lives as a race, where everyone is on their own path to some form of success, we must relearn to value the connections we make along the track.
我们不应把人生视为一场赛跑——在这场赛跑中，人人都在各自的道路上奔向某种形式的成功——而必须重新学会珍视我们在跑道上建立的人际联系。
We must reevaluate the harm of radical, individual freedom.
我们必须重新评估极端的个人自由带来的危害。
Radical individualism elevates the freedom of the individual over the collective.
极端个人主义把个人的自由置于集体之上。
It argues, for instance, that universal healthcare, an example of collectivism, threatens the dream of many Americans.
例如，它认为全民医保（集体主义的一个例子）威胁着许多美国人的梦想。
Many of us have fallen victim to an individualistic culture.
我们中的许多人已经沦为个人主义文化的牺牲品。
Society tends to celebrate personal achievement and commend it based on the assumption that winning or succeeding is a consequence of working harder than the next person.
社会往往颂扬个人成就并加以称许，依据的是这样一种假设：获胜或成功是比别人更努力的结果。
As a society, we idolize the concept of “losing friends on the road to success”.
我们整个社会都对“在通往成功的路上失去朋友”这一观念推崇备至。
I remember hearing in high school, “Don’t worry about losing friendships; just focus on study and getting into college.
我记得上高中时听人说过：“别为失去友谊而担心，只管专心学习、考上大学。
That’s all that will matter in the long run,” a sentiment that is not unique to my experience.
从长远来看，只有这些才重要。”听到过这种看法的并不只有我一个人。
It’s preached in many success stories, and it’s embedded in the way we see growth.
许多成功故事都在宣扬这种看法，它也深植于我们看待成长的方式之中。
Motivational speakers will push their audience to be complacent about the inevitable end of losing friends.
励志演说家会鼓动听众对失去朋友这一必然结局心安理得。
Spend too much time with friends?
和朋友待在一起的时间太多了？
You’re losing time better utilized on your achievements.
你这是在浪费本可以更好地用来取得成就的时间。
Invest time in your relationships?
把时间投入到人际关系上？
Invest time in your work instead.
还是把时间投入到工作上吧。
This constant need to succeed has blinded us from seeing through the whirlwind of change that accompanies our everyday lives.
这种时刻都要成功的需求蒙蔽了我们的双眼，让我们看不透伴随日常生活而来的旋风般的变化。
We are expected to tangibly succeed, earn awards, get higher positions, earn better grades.
人们期望我们取得实实在在的成功，赢得奖项，获得更高的职位，取得更好的成绩。
In order to succeed, we lose friends, and that has sadly become normalized.
为了成功，我们失去朋友，而可悲的是，这已经成了常态。
We cannot be complacent with losing friendships because they are our anchors.
我们不能对失去友谊心安理得，因为友谊是我们的依靠。
Yes, pursue success.
没错，去追求成功吧。
Challenge yourself.
挑战自我。
Push limits.
突破极限。
But contrary to all the self-proclaimed success experts, doing it alone does not make you more successful or any better than someone who achieved it with the help of others.
但与所有自封的成功学专家所说的相反，单打独斗并不会让你比借助他人帮助取得成功的人更成功，也丝毫不会让你比人家更优秀。
Put effort into fostering healthy relationships, and maintaining them through your busy schedule that seems like it leaves no time for anyone else.
要下功夫培养健康的人际关系，即使日程繁忙得似乎没给其他任何人留下时间，也要维系好这些关系。
Although we may be living in a society that treasures the independent pursuit of achievement, having people to support and love you on the way is far more important than any end result.
尽管我们可能正生活在一个珍视独立追求成就的社会中，但一路上有人支持你、爱你，远比任何最终结果都重要。